HBS Archives Photograph Collection: Faculty and Staff, 1908-2005: A Finding Aid
HBS Archives Photograph Collection: Faculty and Staff, 1908-2005
- Series I. Faculty Photographs, 1908-2005
  - Subseries A. Faculty Photographs, A-Z, 1908-2005
    - Gordon Donaldson, 1950s (Box 9)
    - Gordon Donaldson, 1980s (Box 9)
    - Michael B. Donham, circa 1980 (Box 9)
    - Paul Donham, 1938-1955 (Box 9)
    - Richard Donham, 1928 (Box 9)
    - Wallace B. Donham- Notes and clippings regarding photographs (Box 9)
    - Wallace B. Donham, circa 1921, (Oversize box) (Box OS 1)
    - Wallace B. Donham, 1927 (Box 9)
    - Wallace B. Donham, 1930s (Box 9)
    - Wallace B. Donham- With Philip Cabot and Ross G. Walker, 1930s (Box 9)
    - Wallace B. Donham- Portrait painting, circa 1935 (Box 9)
    - Wallace B. Donham- With mother-in-law, circa 1940 (Box 9)
    - Wallace B. Donham, 1940s (Box 9)
    - Wallace B. Donham, 1942 (Box 9)
    - Wallace B. Donham- With Everett Needham Case, 1942 (Box 9)
    - Wallace B. Donham- Portrait painting, 1944 (Box 9)
    - Wallace B. Donham- With Donald K. David, ca. 1944 (Box 9)
    - Wallace B. Donham- Weekend Conference on Human Relations, 10-11 May 1947 (Box 9)
    - Wallace B. Donham, circa 1950 (Box 9)
    - Wallace B. Donham- In chair with a pipe, circa 1950 (Box 9)
    - Wallace B. Donham, circa 1950 (Box 9)
      (Photograph possibly mis-identified)
    - Wallace B. Donham- At Weatherbee Lecture, 1951 (Box 9)
    - Wallace B. Donham, Leatherbee Lecture, 1951 (Box 9)
    - Anne Donnellon, 1987 (Box 9)
    - James Doolan, 1970 (Box 9)
    - Arch Richard Dooley, 1956-1977 (Box 9)
    - Georges F. Doriot, 1920s (Box 9)
    - Georges F. Doriot- International Congress of Accountants (Amstedam, Netherlands), 1926 (Box 9)
    - Georges F. Doriot, 1940s (Box 9)
    - Georges F. Doriot, 1942-1943 (Box 9)
    - Georges F. Doriot, 1949 (Box 9)
    - Georges F. Doriot- On cover of Business Week, 19 February 1949 (Box 9)
    - Georges F. Doriot, 1950s (Box 9)
    - Georges F. Doriot- With Manufacturing Group, Spring 1958 (Box 9)
    - Georges F. Doriot- Photograph by Yousuf Karsh, circa 1955, (Oversize folder) (Mapcase)
    - Georges F. Doriot, circa 1960 (Box 9)
    - Georges F. Doriot- In classroom, 1963 (Box 9)
    - Georges F. Doriot- With project team, 1963 (Box 9)
    - Georges F. Doriot, 1964 (Box 9)
    - Georges F. Doriot, 1966 (Box 9)
    - Georges F. Doriot, 1979 (Box 9)
    - Georges F. Doriot- Birthday celebration, 24 September 1979 (Box 9)
    - Georges F. Doriot, 1983 (Box 9)
    - Georges F. Doriot- Teaching, circa 1985, (Oversize box) (Box OS 1)
    - Linda Doyle, 1983 (Box 9)
    - Yves L. Doz, 978 (Box 9)
    - Stuart E. Dreyfus, circa 1970 (Box 10)
    - Minette E. Drumwright, 1989 (Box 10)
    - John T. Dunlap, 1972 (Box 10)
    - John T. Dunlap, 1977 (Box 10)
    - William A. Dwiggins, circa 1917 (Box 10)
    - Davis Dyer, 1985 (Box 10)
    - J. Franklin Ebersole, 1931-1939 (Box 10)
    - Robert G. Eccles, Jr, 1993 (Box 10)
    - George P. Ecker, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Anthony Edwards, circa 1970 (Box 10)
    - Nabil El-Hage, 1985 (Box 10)
    - Charles W. Elliot (1961 copy of an 1872 photograph), 1872 (Box 10)
    - Charles D. Ellis, circa 1970 (Box 10)
    - Richard Ellsworth, circa 1990 (Box 10)
    - William M. Emmons, III, 1986 (Box 10)
    - Dennis J. Encarnation, III, circa 1992 (Box 10)
    - Amy C. Edmondson, 2002 (Box 10)
    - Wilbur B. England, 1950s (Box 10)
    - Wilbur B. England, 1960s (Box 10)
    - Wilbur B. England- Managers' Seminar group photograph, 1963 (Box 10)
    - Wilbur B. England- Presenting the Melvin T. Copeland Award for excellence in marketing to William W. George., 1966 (Box 10)
    - Wilbur B. England, 1991 (Box 10)
    - Kenneth J. English, circa 1960 (Box 10)
    - Ernest J. Enright, 1957 (Box 10)
    - Michael Enright, 1986 (Box 10)
    - Ben Esty, circa 1999 (Box 10)
    - Amatai Etzioni, 1989 (Box 10)
    - John Sinclair Ewing, 1953 (Box 10)
    - John U. Farley, 1985 (Box 10)
    - Jose P. Faus, 1973 (Box 10)
    - Victor A. Faux, circa 1976 (Box 10)
    - John Fayerweather, 1948-1950s (Box 10)
    - William Ward Fearnside, 1958 (Box 10)
    - David W. Fehr, 1978 (Box 10)
    - Edward L. Felton, 1971 (Box 10)
    - Dan H. Fenn, circa 1959 (Box 10)
    - Dan H. Fenn, 1960s (Box 10)
    - Dan H. Fenn, 1972 (Box 10)
    - Steven R. Fenster, circa 1990 (Box 10)
    - Steven R. Fenster, 1993 (Box 10)
    - Donald A. Fergusson, 1956 (Box 10)
    - Charles E. Fisher, 1940s (Box 10)
    - James D. Fleck, 1965 (Box 10)
    - Kenneth U. Flood, 1962 (Box 10)
    - James J. Foley, 1960s (Box 11)
    - Franklin E. Folts, 1947 (Box 11)
    - Franklin E. Folts, 1948 (Box 11)
    - Franklin E. Folts, 1949 (Box 11)
    - Franklin E. Folts, circa 1950 (Box 11)
    - Franklin E. Folts, 1953-1955 (Box 11)
    - Franklin E. Folts, circa 1955 (Box 11)
    - Franklin E. Folts- With Ross G. Walker receiving honorary degree from University of Western Ontario, November 1965 (Box 11)
    - Franklin E. Folts- With Lawrence Fouraker, 1978 (Box 11)
    - Marion F. Foote, 1974 (Box 11)
    - Clifford A. Foster, 1950s (Box 11)
    - Margery Somers Foster, 1959 (Box 11)
      (Taught in Harvard-Radcliffe Program in Business Administration)
    - Fred Foulkes, 1970s (Box 11)
    - Lawrence E. Fouraker, 1960s (Box 11)
    - Lawrence E. Fouraker, 1968 (Box 11)
    - Lawrence E. Fouraker, 1969 (Box 11)
    - Lawrence E. Fouraker, 1970s (Box 11)
    - Lawrence E. Fouraker, 1970 (Box 11)
    - Lawrence E. Fouraker, 1972 (Box 11)
    - Lawrence E. Fouraker, 1973 (Box 11)
    - Lawrence E. Fouraker, 1974 (Box 11)
    - Lawrence E. Fouraker, 1975 (Box 11)
    - Lawrence E. Fouraker, 1976 (Box 11)
    - Lawrence E. Fouraker, 1977 (Box 11)
    - Lawrence E. Fouraker- With Derek Bok and George Lombard, 1977 (Box 11)
    - Lawrence E. Fouraker, 1978 (Box 11)
    - Lawrence E. Fouraker, 1979 (Box 11)
    - Lawrence E. Fouraker, 1981, (Oversize box) (Box OS 1)
    - Lawrence E. Fouraker, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Susan M. Fournier, 1994 (Box 11)
    - Bertrand Fox, 1949-1960s (Box 11)
    - John Bayley Fox, 1938-1948 (Box 11)
    - John Bayley Fox- With Luther Holbrook, Lewis Ward and James Rollins, 1949 (Box 11)
    - John Bayley Fox, 1950s (Box 11)
    - John Roland Fox, 1980s-1990s (Box 11)
    - Ronald E. Frame, circa 1960 (Box 11)
    - Ronald S. Frank, circa 1973 (Box 11)
    - Cecil Eaton Fraser, circa 1925 (Box 11)
    - Cecil Eaton Fraser, circa 1935 (Box 11)
    - Cecil Eaton Fraser, circa 1947 (Box 11)
    - Walter F. Frese, 1957 (Box 11)
    - Walter F. Frese- Teaching, circa 1965 (Box 11)
    - Walter F. Frese, 1976 (Box 11)
    - Sherwood C. Frey, Jr., 1970-1976 (Box 11)
    - Raymond Friedman, 1989-1990s (Box 11)
    - Dennis P. Frolin, 1974 (Box 11)
    - Dennis P. Frolin, 1975 (Box 11)
    - Kenneth A. Froot, 1991-1995 (Box 11)
    - William E. Fruhan, Jr., 1970-1984 (Box 11)
    - William E. Fruhan, Jr., 1989 (Box 11)
    - Mark B. Fuller, circa 1985 (Box 11)
    - Stephen Herbert Fuller- Portraits, circa 1953 (Box 11)
    - Stephen Herbert Fuller- Teaching, 1960s (Box 11)
    - Stephen Herbert Fuller- Presenting award to Charles R. Marshall (MBA 1966), 1965 (Box 11)
    - Stephen Herbert Fuller- Speaking at Associates Placement Conference, 1969 (Box 11)
    - Stephen Herbert Fuller, 1970s (Box 11)
    - Stephen Herbert Fuller, 1980s (Box 11)
    - William E. Fulmer, 1976 (Box 11)
    - Victor Kwok-King Fung, 1973 (Box 11)
    - Edward E. Furash, 1961 (Box 11)
    - John J. Gabarro, 1970s (Box 12)
    - John J. Gabarro, 1980s (Box 12)
    - John J. Gabarro, 1990s (Box 12)
    - Christopher Gale, 1968 (Box 12)
    - James Gammill, 1989 (Box 12)
    - David A. Garvin, circa 1980-1990s (Box 12)
    - Edwin Francis Gay- Clippings (Box 12)
    - Edwin Francis Gay, circa 1908, (Oversize box) (Box OS 1)
    - Edwin Francis Gay, 1908 (Box 12)
    - Edwin Francis Gay, 1920s (Box 12)
    - Edwin Francis Gay, circa 1920, (Oversize box) (Box OS 1)
    - Edwin Francis Gay- Painting by Mary Gay, 1936 (Box 12)
    - Edwin Francis Gay- Painting by Alexander Iacovleff, 1946 (Box 12)
    - Pankaj Ghemawat, 1984 (Box 12)
    - George S. Gibb, 1948-1951 (Box 12)
    - Michael J. Gibbs, 1989 (Box 12)
    - Cyrus F. Gibson, 1980s (Box 12)
    - Robert Gilbertson, 1974 (Box 12)
    - Frederick W. Gill, 1948 (Box 12)
    - Frank Forster Gilmore, 1947-1948 (Box 12)
    - Stuart C. Gilson, 1992 (Box 12)
    - John H. Gladney, Jr., 1980s (Box 12)
    - Frank P. Glass, circa 1935 (Box 12)
    - Robert Glauber, 1970s (Box 12)
    - John D. Glover, 1939 (Box 12)
    - John D. Glover, 1946-1948 (Box 12)
    - John D. Glover, 1950s (Box 12)
    - John D. Glover, 1960s (Box 12)
    - John D. Glover, 1970-1977 (Box 12)
    - Ray Goldberg, 1960s (Box 12)
    - Ray Goldberg- In classroom with students, 1968 (Box 12)
    - Ray Goldberg- In classroom, 1968 (Box 12)
    - Ray Goldberg- On cover of Feed Management, May 1968 (Box 12)
    - Ray Goldberg, 1970s (Box 12)
    - Ray Goldberg, 1970 (Box 12)
    - Ray Goldberg, 1980 (Box 12)
    - Samuel Goldberg, 1961 (Box 12)
    - Clinton S. Golden, 1950s (Box 12)
    - Benjamin Gomes-Casseres, 1985 (Box 12)
    - Edmund Monroe Goodhue, 1983 (Box 12)
    - John B. Goodman, 1989 (Box 12)
    - Kenneth E. Goodpaster, 1989 (Box 12)
    - Lincoln Gordon, 1948-1949 (Box 12)
    - Lincoln Gordon, circa 1950 (Box 12)
    - Lincoln Gordon, circa 1955 (Box 12)
    - Lincoln Gordon, circa 1960 (Box 12)
    - Carey Gordnsen, 1990s (Box 12)
    - William P. Gormbley, Jr., 1955 (Box 12)
    - Malcolm H. Gotterer, 1957 (Box 12)
    - Robert B. Gowing, circa 1948 (Box 12)
    - Charles I. Gragg- Copies of diploma, 1928 (Box 12)
    - Charles I. Gragg, 1946 (Box 12)
    - Charles I. Gragg, 1947-1948 (Box 12)
    - Charles I. Gragg, circa 1950 (Box 12)
    - Charles I. Gragg, circa 1956 (Box 12)
    - Edward Graham, 1970 (Box 12)
    - Margaret B.W. Graham, 1982 (Box 12)
    - Margaret B.W. Graham, 1987 (Box 12)
    - Margaret B.W. Graham- In office, 1987 (Box 12)
    - Norman S.B. Gras- Portrait, circa 1929 (Box 12)
    - Norman S.B. Gras- Portrait, 1929 (Box 12)
    - Norman S.B. Gras, 1941-1949 (Box 12)
    - Norman S.B. Gras- Portrait, 1948 (Box 12)
    - Ann E. Gray, 1993 (Box 12)
    - Jerry Green, 1995 (Box 13)
    - Jerry Greenberg, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Ronald Greenberg, 1982 (Box 13)
    - Ronald K. Greenleaf, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Bruce C. Greenwald, 1982 (Box 13)
    - Barrie Sanford Greiff, circa 1971 (Box 13)
    - Larry E. Greiner, 1966-1969 (Box 13)
    - Stephen A. Greyser, 1963 (Box 13)
    - Stephen A. Greyser, 1966 (Box 13)
    - Stephen A. Greyser, circa 1970 (Box 13)
    - Stephen A. Greyser, circa 1972 (Box 13)
    - Stephen A. Greyser, 1977 (Box 13)
    - Stephen A. Greyser, 1980s (Box 13)
    - Stephen A. Greyser, 1990s (Box 13)
    - Austin Grimshaw, 1935 (Box 13)
    - Robert Grinwald, circa 1983 (Box 13)
    - H. Irving Grousbeck, 1980s (Box 13)
    - William D. Guth, circa 1965 (Box 13)
    - Walter Russell Guthrie, 1943 (Box 13)
    - J. Richard Hackman, 1993-1994 (Box 13)
    - Leigh Hafrey, 1989 (Box 13)
    - James Hagler, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Robert W. Haigh, 1949-circa 1955 (Box 13)
    - Harold R. Hall, circa 1960 (Box 13)
    - Roger H. Hallowell, 1990s (Box 13)
    - Donald G. Halper, 1968 (Box 13)
    - Morris Hamburg, circa 1970 (Box 13)
    - Richard G. Hammermesh, circa 1977- circa 1980 (Box 13)
    - Janice Hammond, 1986 (Box 13)
    - John Hammond, circa 1966 (Box 13)
    - John Hammond, circa 1980-1994 (Box 13)
    - George H. Hanford, 1948 (Box 13)
    - Leslie Hannah, 1985 (Box 13)
    - Harry L. Hansen, 1935-1947 (Box 13)
    - Harry L. Hansen- Teaching, circa 1950 (Box 13)
    - Harry L. Hansen, circa 1960 (Box 13)
    - Harry L. Hansen- Teaching, circa 1965 (Box 13)
    - Harry L. Hansen, 1965 (Box 13)
    - Harry L. Hansen- Receiving Philippine Presidential Medal, 1973 (Box 13)
    - Harry L. Hansen, circa 1980 (Box 13)
    - Harry L. Hansen, circa 1985 (Box 13)
    - Harry L. Hansen, 1985, (Oversize box) (Box OS 1)
    - Harry L. Hansen, circa 1991 (Box 13)
    - Arthur W. Hanson, 1935-1948 (Box 13)
    - Arthur W. Hanson- Teaching accounting class, 1943 (Box 13)
    - Arthur W. Hanson, circa 1949 (Box 13)
    - Arthur W. Hanson- With Charles A. Bliss and Robert O. Schlaifer, circa 1949 (Box 13)
    - Arthur W. Hanson- With Charles A. Bliss, 1949 (Box 13)
    - Arthur W. Hanson, circa 1950 (Box 13)
    - Arthur W. Hanson- Photograph by Yousuf Karsh, circa 1958 (Box 13)
    - Arthur W. Hanson, circa 1960 (Box 13)
    - Anne Harlan, 1975 (Box 13)
    - Neil E. Harlan, circa 1955 (Box 13)
    - Donald L. Hartnett, circa 1968 (Box 13)
    - Kenneth Harris, 1940s (Box 13)
    - James Kaull Hart, circa 1948 (Box 13)
    - Russell H. Hassler, 1960s (Box 13)
    - Russell H. Hassler- With Lillian Cotter, circa 1960 (Box 13)
    - Kenneth J. Hatten, 1976 (Box 13)
    - Michael E. Hattersley, 1988 (Box 13)
    - Oscar Hauptmann, 1989 (Box 13)
    - Jerry A. Hausman, 1987 (Box 13)
    - David F. Hawkins, circa 1965 (Box 13)
    - Arnoldo Cubillo Hax, 1971-1987 (Box 13)
    - Robert Hayes, circa 1967 (Box 13)
    - Robert Hayes, circa 1980 (Box 13)
    - Robert Hayes- With William Abernathy, 1980 (Box 13)
    - Robert Hayes, circa 1983 (Box 13)
    - Robert Hayes- With Kim Clark, circa 1983 (Box 13)
    - Robert Hayes, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Robert Hayes, circa 1985 (Box 13)
    - Robert Hayes, 1988 (Box 13)
    - Robert Hayes, circa 1990 (Box 13)
    - Samuel L. Hayes, circa 1961-circa 1990 (Box 13)
    - Ulric St. Clair Haynes, 1968 (Box 13)
    - William Warren Haynes, 1966 (Box 13)
    - James J. Healy, 1946 (Box 14)
    - James J. Healy, 1956 (Box 14)
    - James J. Healy, 1959 (Box 14)
    - James J. Healy, circa 1960 (Box 14)
    - James J. Healy, 1961 (Box 14)
    - James J. Healy, circa 1963 (Box 14)
    - James J. Healy, circa 1965 (Box 14)
    - Hal Heaton, 1989 (Box 14)
    - [Charles C.] Heckscher, 1990 (Box 14)
    - Lt. Col. John F. Heflin, 1947 (Box 14)
    - David A. Heider, circa 1970 (Box 14)
    - Christine Heckman, circa 1980 (Box 14)
    - Erich A. Helfert, 1961 (Box 14)
    - Lawrence J. Henderson- Portraits, circa 1940 (Box 14)
    - Lawrence J. Henderson, 1940s (Box 14)
    - Margaret M. Hennig, 1970s (Box 14)
    - Julie H. Hertenstein, circa 1980 (Box 14)
    - Regina E. Hertzlinger, 1971-1980s (Box 14)
    - James L. Heskett, 1979 (Box 14)
    - James L. Heskett, circa 1990 (Box 14)
    - James L. Heskett- With Leonard A. Schlesinger, 1991 (Box 14)
    - Ralph Willard Hidy, 1959 (Box 14)
    - Ralph Willard Hidy- Teaching, circa 1960 (Box 14)
    - Ralph Willard Hidy, 1960s (Box 14)
    - Ralph Willard Hidy, 1967 (Box 14)
    - Ralph Willard Hidy- AEC Historical Advisory Committee, 13 May 1968 (Box 14)
    - Ralph Willard Hidy, 1970 (Box 14)
    - Monica Higgins, 1996 (Box 14)
    - Jack C. High, 1993 (Box 14)
    - Bruce M. Hill, circa 1965 (Box 14)
    - Linda Hill, 1985 (Box 14)
    - Linda Hill, circa 1990 (Box 14)
    - Linda Hill, circa 1992 (Box 14)
    - Linda Hill- Teaching, circa 1992 (Box 14)
    - Randall Hiller, 1989 (Box 14)
    - Joseph Hinsey, circa 1990 (Box 14)
    - Richard C. Hodgson, 1964 (Box 14)
    - Richard C. Hodgson, 1983 (Box 14)
    - Edward J. Hoff, circa 1990 (Box 14)
    - Paul M. Hoff, Jr., circa 1965 (Box 14)
    - Luther Gardner Holbrook, 1946-1948 (Box 14)
    - William K. Holstein, 1966 (Box 14)
    - Gerald J. Holtz, circa 1974 (Box 14)
    - George C. Homans, circa 1965 (Box 14)
    - Philip B. Hoppin, 1935-1937 (Box 14)
    - James W. Horwitz, 1932-1935 (Box 14)
    - Murray Horwitz, circa 1965 (Box 14)
    - Windsor Arnold Hosmer, 1935-1937 (Box 14)
    - Windsor Arnold Hosmer, 1940s (Box 14)
    - Windsor Arnold Hosmer, 1948 (Box 14)
    - Windsor Arnold Hosmer- Photograph by Yousuf Karsh, circa 1955, (Oversize folder) (Mapcase)
    - James P. Houchk, circa 1965 (Box 14)
    - Anthony P. Hourihan, circa 1976 (Box 14)
    - David Howard, circa 1940 (Box 14)
    - Ronald Howard, 1980s (Box 14)
    - Robert A. Howell, circa 1968 (Box 14)
    - Ralph Merle Hower, 1937-1948 (Box 14)
    - Ralph Merle Hower, circa 1950-1958 (Box 14)
    - Ralph Merle Hower, 1960s (Box 14)
    - Ralph Merle Hower, 1960s (Box 14)
    - Joseph Bradley Hubbard, 1935-1939 (Box 15)
    - G. David Hughes, 1983 (Box 15)
    - Pearson Hunt, circa 1935-1948 (Box 15)
    - Pearson Hunt- With Robert Anthony and Charles M. Williams, 1949 (Box 15)
    - Pearson Hunt, 1960s (Box 15)
    - Pearson Hunt- Portraits, 1960s (Box 15)
    - Pearson Hunt- Teaching, circa 1965 (Box 15)
    - Pearson Hunt, 1965 (Box 15)
    - Pearson Hunt- Portraits, 1970s (Box 15)
    - Pearson Hunt- Group photograph of Gulf Management Institute, 1978 (Box 15)
    - Pearson Hunt, 1980s (Box 15)
    - Pearson Hunt, 1991 (Box 15)
    - James G. Ingraham, 1950 (Box 15)
    - Nathan Isaacs, 1935-1938 (Box 15)
    - Barbara B. Jackson, circa 1974 (Box 15)
    - Robert K. Jaedicke, circa 1960 (Box 15)
    - Jeff Jaffe, circa 1980 (Box 15)
    - Ramchandran Jaikumar, circa 1985 (Box 15)
    - Ramchandran Jaikumar, 1989 (Box 15)
    - Ramchandran Jaikumar, 1992 (Box 15)
    - Anne Jardim, circa 1973 (Box 15)
    - Bernard Jaworski, circa 1992 (Box 15)
    - Michael C. Jensen, circa 1985 (Box 15)
    - William T. Jerome, circa 1955 (Box 15)
    - John E. Jeuck, circa 1956 (Box 15)
    - Todd D. Jick, 1986 (Box 15)
    - Arthur M. Johnson, circa 1965 (Box 15)
    - Charles E. Johnson, circa 1970 (Box 15)
    - Charles E. Johnson, February 1970 (Box 15)
    - Charles E. Johnson, June 1970 (Box 15)
    - Charles E. Johnson- With George Romney, September 1971 (Box 15)
    - G. G. Johnson, circa 1975 (Box 15)
    - Lawrence A. Johnson, 1976 (Box 15)
    - Thomas Johnson, Jr., circa 1976 (Box 15)
    - Curtis Jones, circa 1963 (Box 15)
    - E. Philip Jones, Jr., circa 1982 (Box 15)
    - Thomas O. Jones, 1994 (Box 15)
    - Norman H. Josephy, circa 1980 (Box 15)
    - James V. Jucker, circa 1975 (Box 15)
    - Andrew S. Kahr, circa 1964 (Box 15)
    - Basil A. Kalymon, circa 1974 (Box 15)
    - Rosabeth Moss Kanter, circa 1986 (Box 15)
    - Donald M. Kaplan, circa 1970 (Box 15)
    - Robert S. Kaplan, circa 1984 (Box 15)
    - J. Barkev M. Kassarjian, circa 1967 (Box 15)
    - Robert L. Katz, 1959 (Box 15)
    - Gordon M. Kaufman, circa 1961 (Box 15)
    - Stuart A. Kauter, circa 1980 (Box 15)
    - Peter G.W. Keen, circa 1973 (Box 15)
    - John Kimball Kehoe, circa 1974 (Box 15)
    - Eugene J. Kelley, circa 1965 (Box 15)
    - Christopher Kellogg, circa 1990 (Box 15)
    - Charles M. Kelso, Jr., 1970s (Box 15)
    - Shildrick A. Kendrick, circa 1950 (Box 15)
    - Thomas Kennedy, circa 1970 (Box 15)
    - Thomas Kennedy- Portraits, circa 1970 (Box 15)
    - Thomas Kennedy, 1976 (Box 15)
    - Thomas Kennedy, 1987 (Box 15)
    - Robert W. Kent, circa 1988 (Box 15)
    - Roger B. Kent, circa 1953 (Box 15)
    - W. Karl Kester, circa 1982 (Box 15)
    - W. Karl Kester, circa 1990 (Box 15)
    - Manfred F.R. Kets de Vries, 1980s (Box 15)
    - Maurice D. Kilbridge, 1960s (Box 15)
    - Alva F. Kindall, circa 1980 (Box 16)
    - Thomas C. Kinnear, circa 1985 (Box 16)
    - Adam Klein, circa 1988 (Box 16)
    - Janice A. Klein, circa 1984 (Box 16)
    - Norman Klein, circa 1990 (Box 16)
    - Robert Eugene Klippel, circa 1972 (Box 16)
    - Frederick T. Knickerbocker, circa 1972 (Box 16)
    - Tomas Kohn, circa 1995 (Box 16)
    - Marshall R. Kolin, circa 1962 (Box 16)
    - David C. Korten, circa 1970 (Box 16)
    - John P. Kotter, circa 1974 (Box 16)
    - John P. Kotter, circa 1980 (Box 16)
    - John P. Kotter, circa 1985 (Box 16)
    - John P. Kotter, 1990 (Box 16)
    - William S. Krasner, circa 1980 (Box 16)
    - Jurgen Ladendorf, circa 1965 (Box 16)
    - Charles Chester Lane (1979 copy of photograph), circa 1912 (Box 16)
    - Leonard C.R. Langer, circa 1953 (Box 16)
    - Henrietta Larson, 1942 (Box 16)
    - Henrietta Larson, circa 1950 (Box 16)
    - Henrietta Larson, 1961 (Box 16)
    - Henrietta Larson, 1965 (Box 16)
    - Henrietta Larson, circa 1970 (Box 16)
    - Henrietta Larson- Receiving Distinguished Service Award from Lawrence Fouraker, 1979 (Box 16)
    - Richard Larson, 1956-1959 (Box 16)
    - E. Scott Lathrop, circa 1992 (Box 16)
    - Paul F. Larzarsfeld, circa 1950 (Box 16)
    - Warren Law, circa 1960 (Box 16)
    - Paul R. Lawrence- Visiting a factory, circa 1960 (Box 16)
    - Paul R. Lawrence, 1960s (Box 16)
    - Paul R. Lawrence- Portraits, 1960s (Box 16)
    - Paul R. Lawrence- Teaching, circa 1980 (Box 16)
    - Paul R. Lawrence, 1980s (Box 16)
    - Paul R. Lawrence- Joint Research signing in Moscow, 1988 (Box 16)
    - Paul R. Lawrence, 1990s (Box 16)
    - William Lawrence- Photograph dedicated to Wallace B. Donham, 1924 (Box 16)
    - William Lawrence, circa 1930 (Box 16)
    - William Lawrence- Portrait painting, 1930 (Box 16)
    - Gerald C. Leader, circa 1970 (Box 16)
    - Edmund P. Learned, 1940s (Box 16)
    - Edmund P. Learned, 1945-1946 (Box 16)
    - Edmund P. Learned, 1948-1949 (Box 16)
    - Edmund P. Learned, 1952 (Box 16)
    - Edmund P. Learned- Photograph by Yousuf Karsh, circa 1956 (Box 16)
    - Edmund P. Learned, 1956 (Box 16)
    - Edmund P. Learned, 1960s (Box 16)
    - Edmund P. Learned, 1967 (Box 16)
    - Edmund P. Learned, circa 1970 (Box 16)
    - Edmund P. Learned- Receiving Distinguished Alumni Award, 1975 (Box 16)
    - Robert W. Le Duc, circa 1976 (Box 16)
    - Charles M. Leighton, circa 1965 (Box 16)
    - David S. R. Leighton, circa 1960 (Box 16)
    - Dorothy A. Leonard-Barton, circa 1984 (Box 16)
    - Robert A. Leone, circa 1974-1979 (Box 16)
    - Joseph T. Leverich, circa 1965 (Box 16)
    - Harry Levinson, circa 1968 (Box 16)
    - Theodore Levitt- Teaching, 1960s (Box 16)
    - Theodore Levitt, circa 1961 (Box 16)
    - Theodore Levitt, 1966 (Box 16)
    - Theodore Levitt- On cover of Business Week magazine, 11 March 1967 (Box 16)
    - Theodore Levitt, 1968 (Box 16)
    - Theodore Levitt, circa 1970 (Box 16)
    - Theodore Levitt, 1970s (Box 16)
    - Theodore Levitt, 1983 (Box 16)
    - Theodore Levitt, circa 1999 (Box 16)
    - Wilbur G. Lewellen, circa 1970 (Box 16)
    - Howard Thompson Lewis, 1935-1948 (Box 16)
    - Howard Thompson Lewis- On cover of Purchasing magazine, March 1938 (Box 16)
    - Howard Thompson Lewis, 1940 (Box 16)
    - Howard Thompson Lewis, 1944 (Box 16)
    - Howard Thompson Lewis- Photograph by Yousuf Karsh, 1958 (Box 16)
    - Howard Thompson Lewis- Photograph by Yousuf Karsh, 1958, (Oversize folder) (Mapcase)
    - Ralph F. Lewis, 1960s (Box 16)
    - Robert W. Lewis, circa 1960 (Box 16)
    - Joseph Stoner Lichty, 1939 (Box 16)
    - Thomas B. Lifson, circa 1979 (Box 16)
    - Jay O. Light, circa 1971 (Box 16)
    - Jay O. Light, 1974 (Box 16)
    - Jay O. Light- Portraits, 1989 (Box 16)
    - Jay O. Light- Speaking at Alumni Council Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1989 (Box 16)
    - Jay O. Light, 1990s (Box 16)
    - Patrick R. Liles, circa 1968-1977 (Box 17)
    - Thomas Lilley, 1948 (Box 17)
    - Ban Askel Lindberg, circa 1947 (Box 17)
    - Ben A. Lindberg- With Julius S. Livingston, Howard T. Lewis, and John McLean, circa 1950 (Box 17)
    - Jane C. Linder, circa 1989 (Box 17)
    - John V. Lintner, 1948 (Box 17)
    - John V. Lintner, 1952 (Box 17)
    - John V. Lintner Teaching in classroom, circa 1960 (Box 17)
    - John V. Lintner, circa 1960 (Box 17)
    - John V. Lintner, 1966 (Box 17)
    - John V. Lintner, 1978 (Box 17)
    - John V. Lintner, 1980s (Box 17)
    - John V. Lintner, 1990s (Box 17)
    - James S. Lipscomb, circa 1962 (Box 17)
    - Joseph P. Littlefield, circa 1953 (Box 17)
    - George H. Litwin, circa 1964 (Box 17)
    - E. Robert Livernash, 1956 (Box 17)
    - E. Robert Livernash, circa 1960 (Box 17)
    - E. Robert Livernash, circa 1970 (Box 17)